Hello my name is kapil from group no 1 .
Kapil, I'm group 1. Today I've presenting
the demo video.
Import libraries which are essential
pandas numpy method and see
what loading data set.
Then after check some missing value, we
verified data types and understood the
data size and what.
Then after combined
the title and
body of features
then remove the
non-english review for
better modeling model
function, better functional
model then.
I do feature engineering to
remove the URL, hashtags, numbers,
punctuation, space key on the
extra remove spaces and then
put it into a plain
text. So
after that I
have 1412.
1412 data set. So I
do some PDA exploratory data
analysis. Inside that I find
the bar plot for rating
how many, how many are.
How many, how many, how many
positives and how many negatives?
From 1:00 to 1:00 to
5:00 inside that we see
I see a text length
observing verifiable variation in length
review. Long review are often
more detail and sentiment.
Then boxplot of rating and
text length. High rating tend
to be high, moderate length
review. Very long
review, sometimes indicating mixed or
negative sentiments.
Sentiment mapping.
Sentiment mapping measure majority of.
Reviews are positive and few negatives
are few. Fewer negative and neutral
reviews. Classes imbalance. Then
after I do boxplot for
text and text length and
V sentiment analysis, negative review
are often long and more
descriptive. And positive reviews
are usually short and direct.
After that correlation analysis, text
based feature play a more
important role than numeric.
What are sentiment analysis?
So. Generate
sentiment score, positive, neutral,
negative compound score.
So I have 72% accuracy of
voter sentiment analysis. Short sentence
social media like text.
Inside. Stop
words so reducing
noise improve meaningful
words represent.
Then after train test split
into 80% into train and
20% into.
Then after that tfidf feature
is extraction. So convert
into text into numeric numerical
for using tfidf. Major important.
Out of Word is a documentary
relative of data reducing impact of
common words. This type is critical
based on our model.
Can't process raw text.
So model training and evaluation.
Also inside the model training
logistic regression multinomial multi
nominee. Linear Support
vector classification, Random forest team
gradient boosting. This kind of model
I used.
After that I see some accuracy
all over all that.
Although.
I am so bad. From
all the model evaluation I
see Linear Support Vector classification
is best. It gives 8581%
of accuracy.
So. After that.
After that classification report
insights. Precision
value recall. Is
high handle high dimension TF IDF
data?Robust
against Robust against
overfitting.
Confusion matrix. Strong
performed in Class 2. Positive.
Some confusion between neutral and
negative model. Predict dominant class
more confidently.
Then I dumped into TFIDF
pickle pickle file and sweet
vector and SVC open sentiment
model pick 5.
So this is the.
Streamlet UI code.
And this is the API. I also
use API for that.